

## SHUKHRAT MAKSUDOV

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

### **CONTACT INFO**

- +998 94 214 88 73
- mshukhrat707@gmail.com
- 🕠 github.com/MSLuckyBoy
- twitter.com/MS LuckvBov
- www.facebook.com/profile.php1
- www.instagram.com/ms.luckyboy
- t.me/MS\_LuckyBoy

## **SKILLS**

PYTHON DJANGO

JAVASCRIPT

HTML / CSS

GIT

BLENDER 3D

UNITY 3D

C#

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP WORD / EXEL

LANGUAGES

### **UZBEK**

**SPEAKING** 

LISTENING READING

WRITING

**RUSSIAN** 

**SPEAKING** 

LISTENING

READING

WRITING

**ENGLISH** 

ENGLISE

SPEAKING LISTENING

**READING** 

WRITING

### **ABOUT ME**

Hello! My name is Shukhrat and I am 21 years old. I have been involved in programming for 2 years. My main programming language is python. I use the Python programming language to backend the websites and program various Telegram bots. I use Django freamwork when programming the backend part. Sometimes I also do freelancing.

I also do 3D modeling and Game creation. I can work with programs like Blender and Unity. Basically I am very interested in creating mobile games!

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **UZBEKISTAN RAILWAYS**

2018 - 2019

### **FREELANCER**

2020 - Present

#### **CARGO RECEPTIONIST**

\_

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

I run my freelancing business at Freelancehunt.com. To date, I have successfully completed several Telegram bots and one web site.

### **EDUCATION**

## TASHKENT VOCATIONAL COLLEGE OF RAILWAY TRANSPORT

2016 - 2019

TASHKENT UNIVERSITY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES

2019 - 2021

# MOVEMENT ORGANIZATION AND MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST

-

### **SOFTWARE ENGINEERING**

After successfully completing the 2nd year, I left the university voluntarily in December 2021.

### **AWARDS**

## ONE MILLION UZBEK CODERS & UDACITY

December 2021

## FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT TRACK



## ONE MILLION UZBEK CODERS & UDACITY

December 2021

## FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT TRACK (COMPLETED)

